A Guide to the The Personal Papers of Dorothea E. Abbott, 1950-1999
Arlington Public Library, Center for Local History
- Virginia Counties and Localities
  - James City County: Clippings, 1982-1994 (Box 20)
  - King George County: Clippings (Box 20)
  - Lancaster County: Clippings, Brochures, 1980-1992 (Box 20)
  - Mathews County and Mecklenburg County: Clippings, Brochures, 1981-1989 (Box 20)
  - Middlesex County: Brochures, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Nelson county: Clippings, Brochures (Box 20)
  - Northhampton County and Northumberland County: Clippings, 1983-1991 (Box 20)
  - Orange County: Clippings, Brochures, 1984-1990 (Box 20)
  - Page County: Clippings, Brochure, 1959-1987 (Box 20)
  - Pittsylvania County: Clippings, Brochures, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Prince George County: Clippings, Brochures, 1978-1989 (Box 20)
  - Prince William County: Brochures (Box 20)
  - Prince William County: Clippings, 1983-1995 (Box 20)
  - Rappahannock County: Clippings, Brochures, 1985-1988 (Box 20)
  - Roanoke: Clippings, Brochures, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Rockbridge County: Clippings, Brochures, 1974-1994 (Box 20)
  - Rockingham County: Brochures (Box 20)
  - Scott County and Stafford County: Clippings, Brochures, 1988-1994 (Box 20)
  - Shenandoah County: Clippings, Brochures, 1980-1991 (Box 20)
  - Surry County: Clippings, Brochures, 1985-1987 (Box 20)
  - Tazewell County: Clippings, Brochures, 1981 (Box 20)
  - Washington County: Clippings, Brochures, Notes, 1982-1991 (Box 20)
  - Wise County and York County: Clippings, Brochures, 1983 (Box 20)
- Florida Clippings, Notes, and Brochures
  - Alva: Clipping, 1990 (Box 21)
  - Arcadia: Clippings, 1996 (Box 21)
  - Black Gold: Clippings, 1989 (Box 21)
  - Boca Grande: Clippings, 1990 (Box 21)
  - Boca Raton: Clippings, 1995 (Box 21)
  - Bonita: Clippings, 1997-1998 (Box 21)
  - Cape Coral: Clipping, 1997 (Box 21)
  - Captiva Island: Clippings, Brochures, 1995-1997 (Box 21)
  - Charlotte County: Clippings, Brochures, 1989-1998 (Box 21)
  - Chiefland: Clipping, 1996 (Box 21)
  - Cleveland: Clipping, 1996 (Box 21)
  - DeFuniak Springs: Clipping, 1998 (Box 21)
  - DeLand: Clipping, 1994 (Box 21)
  - DeSoto: Clippings, 1997 (Box 21)
  - El Jobean: Clippings, 1997 (Box 21)
  - Englewood: Clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 21)
  - Estero: Clippings, 1994-1996 (Box 21)
  - Everglades: Clippings, 1990-1998 (Box 21)
  - Fort Myers: Brochures, Maps (Box 21)
  - Fort Myers: Clippings, 1990-1998 (1) (Box 21)
  - Fort Myers: Clippings, 1990-1998 (2) (Box 21)
  - Fort Myers: Clippings, 1990-1998 (3) (Box 21)
  - Fort Myers: Clippings, 1990-1998 (4) (Box 21)
  - Fort Myers: Clippings, 1990-1998 (5) (Box 21)
  - Fort Ogden: Clippings, 1995 (Box 21)
  - Gainsville: Clippings, Brochures, Photos, 1986-1996 (Box 22)
  - Gasparilla Island: Clippings, 1989-1996 (Box 22)
  - Glades County: Clippings, 1989-1996 (Box 22)
  - History of Florida: Clippings, 1990 (Box 22)
  - Indians: Clippings, Notes, Brochure, 1990-1998 (Box 22)
  - Jacksonville: Clippings, 1987-1996 (Box 22)
  - Jupiter Inlet Lighthouse: Clipping, Brochures (Box 22)
  - Key West: Clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 22)
  - Kissimmee: Clippings, Brochure, 1995-1998 (Box 22)
  - Lake Wales, Polk county: Clipping, 1996 (Box 22)
  - Lee County: Clippings, 1991-1998 (Box 22)
  - Lehigh Acres: Clippings, 1989-1996 (Box 22)
  - Manasota Key: Clipping, 1997 (Box 22)
  - Manasota County: Clippings, 1997 (Box 22)
  - Maps of Florida, 1975-1995 (Box 22)
  - Miami: Clippings, Brochures, 1991-1996 (Box 22)
  - Mount Dora: Brochure (Box 22)
  - Mundock: Clippings, 1996 (Box 22)
  - Naples: Clippings, 1993-1998 (Box 22)
  - Nokomis-Spanish Point: Clipping (Box 22)
  - North Port: Clippings, Brochure, 1991-1995 (Box 22)
  - Okeechobee Lake: Clippings, 1990-1996 (Box 22)
  - Orlando: Clippings, Map, 1991-1994 (Box 22)
  - Ormond Beach-Daytona Beach: Clippings, Notes, 1983-1988 (Box 22)
  - Palmdale: Brochure (Box 22)
  - Pensacola, Elgin Air Force Base: Clippings, 1987-1998 (Box 22)
  - Pine Island: Clippings, Brochure, 1991-1998 (Box 22)
  - Port Charlotte and Harbor: Clippings, 1992-1998 (Box 22)
  - Punta Gorda: Brochures (Box 23)
  - Punta Gorda: Clippings, 1988-1998 (1) (Box 23)
  - Punta Gorda: Clippings, 1988-1998 (2) (Box 23)
  - Roads: Clippings, 1992-1997 (Box 23)
  - Ruskin: Clipping, 1992-1994 (Box 23)
  - Sanibel Island: Clippings, Brochures, 1993-1997 (Box 23)
  - Sarasota: Clippings, Brochures, 1988-1996 (Box 23)
  - Southwest Post offices, Airport: Clippings, 1992-1996 (Box 23)
  - St. Augustine: Clippings, Brochures, Post Cards, 1992-1995 (Box 23)
  - Tallahassee: Brochures, Notes, Map, 1983-1991 (Box 23)
  - Tallahassee: Clippings, 1973-1998 (Box 23)
  - Tampa: Clippings, Brochures, 1990-1996 (Box 23)
  - Venice: Clipping, 1997 (Box 23)
  - Vero Beach, 1997 (Box 23)
  - West Palm Beach: Clippings, Brochures, 1991-1996 (Box 23)
  - Winter Park: Clippings, Brochures, 1997 (Box 23)
  - Ybor City: Clippings, Brochures, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Zolfo Springs: Clippings, Brochures, 1997 (Box 23)
- Miscellaneous Topics
  - Archeology: Clippings, 1993-1996 (Box 24)
  - Architecture: Clippings, 1976-1991 (Box 24)
  - Archival Management: Notes (Box 24)
  - Art and Architecture in Canada: Clippings, 1980-1986 (Box 24)
  - Art in France: Clippings, 1968-1995 (Box 24)
  - Art in Holland: Clippings, 1974-1982 (Box 24)
  - Art: U.S.: Clippings, 1968-1992, 1997 (1) (Box 24)
  - Art: U.S.: Clippings, 1968-1992, 1997 (2) (Box 24)
  - Art, Miscellaneous: Clippings, 1968-1993 (1) (Box 24)
  - Art, Miscellaneous: Clippings, 1968-1993 (2) (Box 24)
  - Artists: Clippings, 1937-1993 (1) (Box 25)
  - Artists: Clippings, 1937-1993 (2) (Box 25)
  - Artists: Clippings, 1937-1993 (3) (Box 25)
  - Blacks: Clippings, 1973-1989 (Box 25)
  - Christopher Columbus: Clippings, 1986-1992 (Box 25)
  - Copyright Information, 1990-1992 (Box 25)
  - Cuba: Clippings, 1993-1998 (Box 25)
  - Customs Houses: New Orleans, Charleston, etc.: Pamphlets, Notes, Clippings, 1970-1986 (Box 25)
  - Customs Houses: U.S. and Maryland: Pamphlets, Clippings, Photos, 1983-1985 (Box 25)
  - Egypt: Clippings, 1968-1995 (Box 25)
  - State of Franklin: Notes, Photocopies, Clippings, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Georgia: Clippings (Box 25)
  - Germany: Calendar (Box 26)
  - Great Britain: Clippings, 1968-1995 (1) (Box 26)
  - Great Britain: Clippings, 1968-1995 (2) (Box 26)
  - Indians: Clippings, 1974-1995 (Box 26)
  - Indians: Magazine Articles, 1894, 1948, 1973-1988 (Box 26)
  - Indians: Notes (Box 26)
  - Indians in Virginia: Clippings, 1988-1996 (Box 26)
  - Inventions: Clippings, 1973-1994 (Box 26)
  - Ireland: Clippings, 1968-1986 (Box 26)
  - Italy: Clippings, 1968-1996 (Box 26)
  - Nature, Audubon: Clippings, 1974-1977 (Box 26)
  - New England: Clippings, 1976-1982 (Box 26)
  - Notes on North Carolina (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous Notes re: Tudors, Francis Drake, Roanoke Island (Box 26)
- Northern Virginia Historical Groups
  - Arlington Beautification Committee
    - Minutes, Agendas, 1986-1992 (Box 27)
  - Arlington Boathouse Coalition
    - Proposal, Clipping, 1991 (Box 27)
  - Arlington Heritage Alliance
    - Formation Documents, 1989-1990 (1) (Box 27)
    - Formation Documents, 1989-1990 (2) (Box 27)
    - Board of Directors Minutes and Agendas, n.d., 1990 1990-1995 (1) (Box 27)
    - Board of Directors Minutes and Agendas, n.d., 1990 1990-1995 (2) (Box 27)
    - Board of Directors Minutes and Agendas, n.d., 1990 1990-1995 (3) (Box 27)
    - Board of Directors Minutes and Agendas, n.d., 1990 1990-1995 (4) (Box 27)
    - General Minutes, 1989-1994 (1) (Box 27)
    - General Minutes, 1989-1994 (2) (Box 27)
    - Newsletters, 1990-1994 (Box 27)
    - Flyers and Brochures, 1990-1991 (Box 27)
    - Arlington Historic Properties, 1989-1993 (1) (Box 28)
    - Arlington Historic Properties, 1989-1993 (2) (Box 28)
    - Preservation Articles, 1979-1993 (1) (Box 28)
    - Preservation Articles, 1979-1993 (2) (Box 28)
    - Preservation Clippings, 1973, 1987 (Box 28)
  - Arlington Historical Society
    - Treasurer's Reports, Agendas, 1973-1987 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, Notes, Photographs, 1981-1992 (Box 28)
  - Arlington County Historic Affairs and Landmark Review Boards
    - Procedures, Correspondence, Notes, Report, 1985-1992 (Box 28)
  - National Capital Planning Commission
    - News, 1991-1993 (Box 29)
    - News, 1994 (Box 29)
    - News, 1995-1996 (Box 29)
    - News, 1997-1999 (Box 29)
  - Preservation Alliance of Virginia
    - Materials for a workshop, 1990 (Box 29)
  - Virginia Conference Historical Society
    - Minutes, 1992-1995 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 29)